A Guide to the Governor Gerald L. Baliles Executive Papers, 1986-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Miscellaneous (accession 33707)
  - Sub-Series C: Publications
    - Review of Information Technology in Virginia State Government (Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission), 1988 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Leesburg Today, 2 December 1988 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - National Guard, December 1986 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Radford University (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - City of Richmond (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Address of Charles S. Robb, Governor, to the General Assembly of Virginia, 8 January 1986 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Science Technology and the Constitution (Office of Technology Assessment), September 1987 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Shenandoah National Park (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Smyth County (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report of the State Treasurer of Virginia, 30 June 1986 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - The Supreme Court, The Bill of Rights and the Law (Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Theatre IV (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - A Solvable Problem: Transportation in Northern Virginia (Elinor Schwartz), nd (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Virginia (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - City of Virginia Beach (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Board of Elections, 1986 and 1988 Annual Reports (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Cases and Teaching Notes in International Business (Virginia Center for World Trade), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Tour Directory, 1987-1988 (Virginia Commission for the Arts) (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Pursuing the American Dream: A History of the Development of the Virginia Community College System, 1987 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - History, 1965-1987 (Virginia Council on the Status of Women) (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - A Report on Virginia's Industry of Agriculture (Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services), 1987 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Indians: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, 1987 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Military Institute (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part one) (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part two) (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Virginia State of the Judiciary Report, 1986 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - The Virginia Statute for Religious Freedom, 1786 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Union University Today, 1986/1986 (Box 199, Folder 5)
- Oversize - Series I: 1986
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - Colleges and Universities
    - George Mason University - Vicinity Map of George Mason University, highlighting proposed 94 acre addition to campus, November 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Oversize - Series II: 1987
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1987 September 29 - Map of Proposed Blackwood Industrial Park, Norton, Wise County, Virginia, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)